var strangerThings = [
    {
        question: "Where does Season 1's suspenseful opening scene take place?",
        choices: ["Laboratory", "Spaceship", "The Byer's House", "A creepy farm in the middle of nowhere"],
        correctAnswer: "0",
        img: ""
    },
    {
        question: "Where does the story occur?",
        choices: ["Kansas", "Indiana", "New York", "Texas"],
        correctAnswer: "1",
        img: ""
    },
    {
        question: "Name the game that boys are always playing",
        choices: ["Dungeon & Dragons", "Super Mario Bros", "The Legend of Zelda", "Pac-Man"],
        correctAnswer: "0",
        img: ""
    },
    {
        question: "What is El's favorite food?",
        choices: ["Eggos", "Twinkies", "Pop-Tarts", "Ice cream"],
        correctAnswer: "0",
        img: ""
    },
    {
        question: "The Hawkins National Laboratory who kidnapped Eleven and unleashing the monster poses is connected to to?",
        choices: ["The Department of Health and Human Services", "The Department of Homeland Security", "The Department of Energy", "The Department of Defense"],
        correctAnswer: "",
        img: ""
    },
    {
        question: "What is Eleven's superpower?",
        choices: ["Superhuman Strength", "Telepathy", "Telekinesis", "Superhuman Speed"],
        correctAnswer: "2",
        img: ""
    },
    {
        question: "What do the boys call the terrifying, faceless creature",
        choices: ["Sauron", "Godzilla", "The Thing", "Demogorgon"],
        correctAnswer: "3",
        img: ""
    },
    {
        question: "How does Joyce communicate with herson Will when he is taken? ",
        choices: ["By painting on the wall", "With christmas lights", "Through sensory deprivation", "Through a mirror"],
        correctAnswer: "1",
        img: ""
    },
    {
        question: "What is the name of Mikes's sister?",
        choices: ["Nancy", "Barb", "Ellie", "Millie"],
        correctAnswer: "0",
        img: ""
    },
    {
        question: "The parallel dimension inhabited by the Demogorgon is referred to as?",
        choices: ["The butterfly effect", "The dark world", "The upside down", "The other place"],
        correctAnswer: "2",
        img: ""
    },
];

var strangerState = {
    // userChoice: "",
    // correctMe: "",
    // wrongAnswer: "",
    // images: "",
    points: "",
    timer: "",
    currentQuestion:0


};

var time = 15;

$(document).ready(function () {

    $("#start").on("click", function () {
        $("#start").hide();
        console.log("start");
        counter = setInterval(timer, 1000);

        question();
        timer();
        choices();
    });
});

function question() {

    $("#question").text(strangerThings[strangerState.currentQuestion].question);

}


function choices() {
    var choicesArr = strangerThings[strangerState.currentQuestion].choices;

    for (i = 0; i < choicesArr.length; i++) {
        var buut = $("#choice" + i);
        buut.text(choicesArr[i]);
    }
}

function timer() {
    time--;
    if (time <= 0) {
        clearInterval(counter);
        return;
    }
    $("#timer").html("<h3>" + "Timer : " + time + "</h3>");


}



// $("button").on("click", function (r) {
//     console.log("dave dummy");
//     strangerState.userChoice = strangerThings.choices;
//     // strangerThings[0].correctAnswer;
//     if (strangerState.userChoice != strangerThings[0].correctAnswer) {
       
//         // alert("wrong");
//     } else if (strangerState.userChoice === strangerThings[0].correctAnswer) {
//       points++;
//         // alert("correct");
//     }



// });

$("#choice0").on("click", function(){
    handleUserChoice(0);
    console.log("1");
})

$("#choice1").on("click", function(){
    handleUserChoice(1);
    console.log("2");
})

$("#choice2").on("click", function(){
    handleUserChoice(2);
    console.log("3");
})

$("#choice3").on("click", function(){
    handleUserChoice(3);
    console.log("4");
})



function handleUserChoice(userChoice)
{
    if(userChoice == strangerThings[strangerState.currentQuestion].correctAnswer) {
        console.log("right");

    }else {
        console.log("wrong");
    }
}


function correctGuess() {
    strangerState.correctMe = strangerThings[0].correctAnswer;
    console.log("correct");
}
